<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Search><pages Count="22"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[Written and illustrated by:
                                   W     r i t t e   n    a  n   d    i l l u s  t r  a  t e   d     b  y  :



                                                                             A
                                                                     e
                                                                        n
                                                                                          r
                                                                                            a
                                                                                 m
                                                                                      a
                                                    a
                                                       r
                                                 Sarra Ben Amara
                                                 S

                                                                 B
                                                          r
                                                            a]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[Chapter 1







           "The Arrival of Hyperbot"]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[It  was  just  another  normal  day  in  Ultrapolis,  but  everything



    changed  when  Hyperbot,  the  most  advanced  robot  ever


    created, arrived in Max and Lilla's neighborhood. He wasn't just


    a  regular  robot.  Hyperbot  could  ultracommunicate,  using



    signals  far  beyond  the  speed  of  light.  His  purpose  was  to


    proactively help the city, preventing any future issues before



    they occurred.]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[But there was a problem. Across town, the Antobots



     were  stirring  trouble.  They  were  designed  to  work


     antiseptically, removing threats to the city's systems.



     But             now,               they              were               turning                  against                 their


     programming,  disrupting  the  work  of  the  Proto-



     Robots, who were there to protect and build.]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[Max  and  Lilla  watched  from  their  window  as  Hyperbot  zoomed


   past,  flying  high  above  the  subterranean  tunnels  that  connected


   the city.


   "Do you think we can help Hyperbot?" Max asked.



   "Of course! We'll need to prepare ourselves for this mission," said


   Lilla.  She  grabbed  her  backpack,  full  of  gadgets  that  could


   counteract any of the Antobot's tricks.]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[Chapter 2









      "The Anto Rebellion"]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[The rebellion had begun. Antobots were spreading across



    Ultrapolis,  trying  to  reverse  all  the  progress  the  Proto-


    Robotshad  made.  Max  and  Lilla  raced  through  the


    subterranean  tunnels,  avoiding  the  Antobots'  patrols.


    They  could  hear  the  precautionary  sirens  blaring  above


    them, warning the citizens to stay indoors.


    “We  need  to  find  a  way  to  counterattack  before  the


    Antobots  destroy  the  city!”  Hyperbot  said,  his  circuits



    glowing with determination.]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[They  made  their  way  through  the  tunnels,  Hyperbot


   hovering protectively by their side. When they reached



   the  heart  of  the  substructure,  they  found  a  colorful


   prototype machine surrounded by tools. Lilla’s eyes lit


   up. "This must be it! If we can get this machine working,


   we can stop the Antobots!"]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[Hyperbot’s  arms  transformed  again,  this  time  into  tools



   that  Max  and  Lilla  used  to  fix  the  machine.  The  Antobots


   tried  to  sneak  up  on  them,  but  Hyperbot  was  always  one


   step ahead, keeping them safe.]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[Chapter 3









                               "A New Plan"]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[Once  the  prototype  machine  was  activated,  the  team



    was able to slow the Antobots down. But the situation


    was  far  from  over.  Hyperbot  scanned  the  area,


    calculating  their  next  move.  They  needed  to  think



    proactively to stop the Antobots for good.]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[Max, ever the thinker, had a plan.


    "We need to turn the post-production machine into an



    ultrasecure  device.  That  way,  the  Antobots  won't  be


    able to hack it." Lilla nodded.


    "We  could  hide  it  in  the  substructure  of  the  city.



    Beneath all their radars."]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[The substructure beneath Ultrapolis was confusing, filled


    with twists and turns, but Max and Lina were determined.


    "We  need  to  find  the  main  control  room,"  Max  said,


    studying the map.


    Lilla pointed to a spot on the map. "There it is! Let’s go."]]></page><page Index="15"><![CDATA[As  they  navigated  the  substructure,  the  Antobots


   continued  their  mischief,  but  Hyperbot  was  always



   ready  to  help.  His  soft  blue  glow  lit  up  the  dark


   corridors, and his tools helped Max and Lina overcome


   every obstacle.


   Finally, they reached the control room. With Hyperbot’s



   help, they managed to reset the city’s systems, stopping


   the Antobots in their tracks.]]></page><page Index="16"><![CDATA[Chapter 4










      "Victory and Reflection"]]></page><page Index="17"><![CDATA[The  city  of  Ultrapolis  was  peaceful  once  again.  Max  and


   Lilla  walked  happily  through  the  now-quiet  streets,  with


   Hyperbot  hovering  above  them.  The  sunset  painted  the


   sky in shades of orange and pink, and the city lights began


   to twinkle as night fell.



   "That was amazing," Lilla said, smiling at Max.


   Max grinned. "Yeah, we really did it!"]]></page><page Index="18"><![CDATA[Hyperbot,  glowing  softly,  watched  over  the  city  with  a


   satisfied  smile.  The  Antobots  were  defeated,  and



   Ultrapolis  was  safe,  thanks  to  Max,  Lilla,  and  their  new


   robotic friend.]]></page><page Index="19"><![CDATA[As they sat on a bench overlooking the city, Max, Lilla, and


   Hyperbot  knew  that  this  was  just  the  beginning  of  their


   adventures together.]]></page><page Index="20"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="21"/><page Index="22"><![CDATA[All rights reserved ©Online Tutor School
                                           A l l   r i g h t s   r e s e r v e d   © O n l i n e   T u t o r   S c h o o l]]></page></pages></Search>
